<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Alex Antonov</title>
		<link>asiniy.com</link>
		<atom:link href="asiniy.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Book Review - “Learn Python The Hard Way”</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I haven’t read IT-books for a long-long period. I preferred to do humanitarian science instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now it’s time to get back to the IT sector.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My NEXT BIG THING (TM) for 2018 is Data Science. It’s a no-brainer you can’t grab the whole ML/NN/AI stuff in only one year, but I’d say it’s real to learn basic algorithms/libraries in 1 year, even smaller period of time. So, this is where I go to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first book on this road is a famous &lt;a href=&quot;https://learnpythonthehardway.org/&quot;&gt;LPTHW by Z. Shaw&lt;/a&gt;. It’s written for SO newbies. But I haven’t found any other short and concise introductions to Python. This introduction is so basic, but it’s definitely good for grabbing easiest essentials (you have to omit big amount of text optional even for mid-level devs though).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can read my LPTHW solutions here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/asiniy/lpthw&quot;&gt;https://github.com/asiniy/lpthw&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My VERDICT: it’s up to situation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
				<link>asiniy.com/2017/12/17/Learn-Python-The-Hard-Way/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">asiniy.com/2017/12/17/Learn-Python-The-Hard-Way/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Book Review - “Metaprogramming Elixir”</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I haven’t read technical books for a while. Indeed, it was a little exciting to open a programming book after a long list of historical and political ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I did it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I picked a book related to the Metaprogramming in Elixir because I’m facing problems with grasping Elixir metaprogramming too often. I’m the author of 2 Elixir libraries which intensively use metaprogramming &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/asiniy/ecto_state_machine&quot;&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/asiniy/ecto_materialized_path&quot;&gt;[2]&lt;/a&gt; plus one of my projects has Elixir API inside so I’m sure need to know how to metaprogram in Elixir.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pragprog.com/book/cmelixir/metaprogramming-elixir&quot;&gt;C. McCord&lt;/a&gt;’s gave me a lot of context on internal Elixir mechanisms so it’s definitely worth to read. I wouldn’t recite all its details to you but it gave me a lot of answers on my &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;how?&lt;/code&gt; questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My VERDICT: if you want to bring your Elixir to the next level READ THIS BOOK&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
				<link>asiniy.com/2017/09/21/Metaprogramming-Elixir/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">asiniy.com/2017/09/21/Metaprogramming-Elixir/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Book Review - “You don&#39;t know JS&amp;#58; Scope &amp; Closures”</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the second book in the series. I found it helpful. In just 93 pages, “Scope &amp;amp; Closures” deeply covers annoying and “I don’t want to think about that” concepts of javascript.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My takeaways:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Better understanding of variable accessibility, and not for the javascipt only (I opened relative ruby articles immediately after I finished reading about the scope in javascript).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Deeper view at hoisting. I don’t even know how it will help me to develop better applications (declaration before invocation is always a good thing!).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Closures - I got it!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;My key takeaway - impressive JS module “magic” was revealed and became obvious and ordinary to me.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my opinion this book is worth reading. I will read next title following month.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
				<link>asiniy.com/2017/03/13/YDKJS-Scope-and-Closures-Review/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">asiniy.com/2017/03/13/YDKJS-Scope-and-Closures-Review/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Book Review - “You don&#39;t know JS&amp;#58; Up &amp; Going”</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I fucked up with React.js and descended to BEM implementation on my pet project. I met the common problem that average backend developer has when enters to the frontend land: lack of the javascript knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, I know React.js really well, but I face tons of problems (especially with isomorphic JS building) that more Javascript-related than React.js-related. I don’t know ecosystem, I don’t know how to write performant code, I don’t know how the mechanisms really work. That’s why I decided to learn Javascript well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I decided to take something simple on my digging into the javascript. Even simpler than my current knowledge. So, Kyle Simpson’s series “You don’t know JS” looked good at the first glance. And it is, even the simplest first book “Up &amp;amp; Going” gave me some new pieces of knowledge, even if it’s intended to learn programming newcomers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These pieces are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;better understanding of &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;scope&lt;/code&gt; (but I investigated further by following the links provided in that chapter)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;this&lt;/code&gt; identifier - how it’s defined&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;basic knowledge of a &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;prototype&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;closure&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear backend developer, I have an advice for you: if you know the JS basics and know 4 concepts listed above, feel free to skip this book and go directly to the second title “Scope &amp;amp; Closures”.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
				<link>asiniy.com/2017/03/02/YDKJS-Up-and-Going-Review/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">asiniy.com/2017/03/02/YDKJS-Up-and-Going-Review/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Book Review - “Practical Object Oriented Design in Ruby”</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m a self-taught programmer. I found myself to write relatively dirty, difficult to maintain code even couple of years ago. But yeah, it’s a common self-taught programmers problem: we don’t have a timeframe to learn Computer Science basics. We just register to upwork and start to work immediately (after just couple of books and courses, of course). And it’s good!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m happy with my salary but definitely not with the code quality I produce. I decided 2017 to be the first year when I learn Computer Science basics. The first thing to start with - is not algorithms or data structures. The most important thing to start with - is the software design, because in our days the bottleneck is placed inside the developer performance, not in the machine performance itself. Hopefully, I’ll grow hard algorhytmic codebase in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first book I’ve read on software design and software patterns - is the Sandi Metz bestseller &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.poodr.com/&quot;&gt;Practical Object Oriented Design in Ruby&lt;/a&gt;. Let me go through chapters briefly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first chapter gives the basics of OOP: it’s history, prerequisites for creation and so on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second chapter started to unload good code principles to my head. The main question Sandi asks reader here: “How to make everything in ruby” (class, object, method) work like it has a single responsibility? And she also reveals the main benefit of SRP by practical (even a little contrived) example.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Third chapter was a good explanation on how ruby classes are relies on each other. It was wonderful, but extremely brain-melting journey to the dependencies land. The thing I was not happy in this paragraph was lack of &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Concrete&lt;/code&gt; classes definitions, so some googling was necessary there. Main quote from this chapter - &lt;em&gt;Depend on things that change less often than you do&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fourth chapter is the comprehensive description of Law of Demeter - a prompt how to design your codebase in a good way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fifth has an introduction to Duck Typing - a technic to invent and create interface for different classes to make code less coupled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next chapter is about inheritance - the essential concept of the OOP. It tells how does class hierarchy works, and how could it help us to build a better design in our application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seventh was about sharing behaviour with modules (I was the most familiar with it). Just simple stuff - how could I create modules, why do I need to create it et.c.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eight described how to combine objects with composition. Composition is another (instead of inheritance) way of building application design. Its main idea lies on passing one class instance to another to get an awesome structured and maintained design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The final, chapter nine is about how to properly test code in design techniques covered in this book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My verdict: MUST READ. The book is more about programming overall than only ruby. It gives better understanding how does OOP works and helps to programmer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
				<link>asiniy.com/2017/01/01/Practial-Object-Oriented-Design-In-Ruby-Review/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">asiniy.com/2017/01/01/Practial-Object-Oriented-Design-In-Ruby-Review/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>How do I test sessions in ExUnit?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the small recipe I want to share with community. I had a troubles with testing sessions in &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;ExUnit&lt;/code&gt;. I started to google for answer. Only big piece of hard to understand code in &lt;a href=&quot;http://alexmarandon.com/articles/testing_phoenix_controllers/#testing-with-the-default-plug-pipeline&quot;&gt;Testing Phoenix controllers&lt;/a&gt; article by Alex Marandon. But actually, this piece of code didn’t worked, at least to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also found &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/phoenixframework/phoenix/issues/1008&quot;&gt;github issue&lt;/a&gt; in phoenix repo. Chris McCord said there are two ways to test sessions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Use private assigns (I haven’t got it), and&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Make a request to authentication controller to have a &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;conn&lt;/code&gt; with request on response. Let’s do it!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually code is simple, firstly, I wrote a module in test support. It’s about returning &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;conn()&lt;/code&gt; with a session assigned:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-elixir highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;# test/support/signed_conn.ex&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;defmodule&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;MyApp&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;SignedConn&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;do&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;@endpoint&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;MyApp&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Endpoint&lt;/span&gt;

  &lt;span class=&quot;kn&quot;&gt;import&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Phoenix&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;ConnTest&lt;/span&gt;

  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;signed_user_conn&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;do&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;user&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;MyApp&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;no&quot;&gt;Factory&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;create&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:user&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;

    &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;conn&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;()&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;|&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;post&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;sd&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;/your/new_session_path&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;%{&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;sd&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;session&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;%{&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;sd&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;email&quot;&lt;/span&gt;    &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;user&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;email&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;sd&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;password&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;user&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;password&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;})&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can notice, I created a user via &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;ex_machina&lt;/code&gt; and then made a post request to my sessions controller.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, let’s &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;import MyApp.SignedConn&lt;/code&gt; to &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;MyApp.ConnCase&lt;/code&gt; and&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Volia! We can use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;conn()&lt;/code&gt; without any session assigned, but &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;signed_user_conn()&lt;/code&gt; for connections with already assigned user session!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2016 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
				<link>asiniy.com/2016/05/29/How-do-I-test-ExUnit-sessions/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">asiniy.com/2016/05/29/How-do-I-test-ExUnit-sessions/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>How I migrated SPA backend codebase from Rails to Phoenix</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Some time ago I developed a pretty simple SPA with Rails on backend &amp;amp; React.js on the front. It was pretty simple, but (surprisingly for me!) started to grow like on steroids. Rails started to be a bottleneck since one of the customer requirements was not just making application fast. He wanted it to be instant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not a big deal to buy a couple of servers. But 50 ms response isn’t enough for my client. So, I decided to rewrite backend on something else. After long thinking I chose elixir &amp;amp; phoenix.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to share this transition details with you - maybe you can find something interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-to-run-both-rails--elixir-on-the-same-address&quot;&gt;How to run both rails &amp;amp; elixir on the same address?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to run rails &amp;amp; phoenix on the same address to prevent battle with CORS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I solved this by installing &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;nginx&lt;/code&gt; locally &amp;amp; configuring it to serve few servers on the same address. &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;/etc/nginx/conf.d/development.conf&lt;/code&gt; listing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;server {
  listen 80;
  server_name development.local;

  location / {
    proxy_pass http://127.0.0.1:3000; // rails server
  }

  location /api {
    proxy_pass http://127.0.0.1:4000; // phoenix server; as you can notice, my rails server doesn&#39;t have even /api namespace - it was just a rapid prototype
  }
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;restart nginx, add these lines to &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;etc/hosts/&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;# For elixir-to-rails transition
127.0.0.1 development.local
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and you can open &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;http://development.local&lt;/code&gt; in your browser.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
				<link>asiniy.com/2016/04/09/Transition-from-Rails-To-Phoenix/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">asiniy.com/2016/04/09/Transition-from-Rails-To-Phoenix/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>How to migrate from Coffeescript + JSX =&gt; ES6 + JSX</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I maintained an SPA with relatively old frontend. The main trouble was coffeescript - a lot of new things built by ES6 standard and tying process can be a nightmare.
The simplest thing in this case - to move to ES6. Not a big deal, things like &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/decaffeinate/decaffeinate&quot;&gt;decaffeinate&lt;/a&gt; can help you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got a big problem. Decaffeinate can’t work with JSX, but actually coffeescript &amp;amp; JSX are mixed together inside one file. I’ll describe how to migrate below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Preinstall dependencies&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;npm install -g babel-plugin-transform-react-createelement-to-jsx coffee-react lebab babel-cli
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, we have a set of &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;.coffee&lt;/code&gt; files (maybe &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;.cjsx&lt;/code&gt;, that’s up to you). &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;cd&lt;/code&gt; to root directory of these files and:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;find . -name \*.coffee -print | xargs cjsx -bc
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now we have plain old &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;ES5&lt;/code&gt; with ugly &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;React.createElement&lt;/code&gt; inside. Let’s deal with both drawbacks&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mohebifar/lebab&quot;&gt;Lebab&lt;/a&gt; is awesome 5to6 tool. Let’s convert old style to new.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;find . -name \*.js -print | xargs -iFile lebab File -o File
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s time for &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;JSX&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;http://stackoverflow.com/a/36218474/2926641&quot;&gt;Daniel&lt;/a&gt; gave me a hint how to do it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;find . -name \*.js -print | xargs -iFile babel --plugins transform-react-createelement-to-jsx File -o File
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another small thing. &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Coffee-script&lt;/code&gt; package adds a comment to the top of each file it converts. Remove these comments:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;find . -name \*.js -print | xargs -iFile sed -i &#39;1d&#39; File
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last. You are using build tool, aren’t you? So ok, let’s replace &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;.coffee&lt;/code&gt; dependencies by &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;.js&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;find . -name \*.js -print | xargs sed -i &#39;s/.coffee/.js/g&#39;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Volia! Happy ES6!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
				<link>asiniy.com/2016/03/25/Convert-Coffeescript-With-ES5-To-JSX-With-ES6/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">asiniy.com/2016/03/25/Convert-Coffeescript-With-ES5-To-JSX-With-ES6/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
